{
  "688536": {
    "questionText": "…Mr. Brown is … excellent teacher.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359782",
      "answerText": "- … an"
    }
  },
  "688537": {
    "questionText": "I have … two sisters and… brother.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359788",
      "answerText": "- … a"
    }
  },
  "688538": {
    "questionText": "Ann is one of … most beautiful girls in … her group.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359789",
      "answerText": "the … -"
    }
  },
  "688539": {
    "questionText": "I play … piano and my brother plays … football.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359796",
      "answerText": "the … -"
    }
  },
  "688540": {
    "questionText": "… dress she is wearing is … blue.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359799",
      "answerText": "the … -"
    }
  },
  "688541": {
    "questionText": "… Los Angeles is the city of ...USA.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359805",
      "answerText": "- … the"
    }
  },
  "688542": {
    "questionText": "Has … president of … Ukraine ever been to … Netherlands?",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359811",
      "answerText": "the … - … the"
    }
  },
  "688543": {
    "questionText": "… Nile flows into … Mediterranean, doesn’t it?",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359814",
      "answerText": "the … the"
    }
  },
  "688544": {
    "questionText": "… Everest, … highest mountain in the world, is in … Himalayas.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359823",
      "answerText": "- … the … the"
    }
  },
  "688545": {
    "questionText": ".…Lake Baikal is …. world’s oldest and deepest lake.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359827",
      "answerText": "- … the"
    }
  },
  "688546": {
    "questionText": "I … understand him. He should speak louder.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359830",
      "answerText": "can’t"
    }
  },
  "688547": {
    "questionText": "You … be tired because you have worked very hard.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359838",
      "answerText": "must"
    }
  },
  "688548": {
    "questionText": "He … come to my tomorrow’s party because he is ill.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359839",
      "answerText": "will not be able to"
    }
  },
  "688549": {
    "questionText": "I … understand him. He should speak louder.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359845",
      "answerText": "can’t"
    }
  },
  "688550": {
    "questionText": "It is not very important. You … do it now.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359853",
      "answerText": "may not"
    }
  },
  "688551": {
    "questionText": ".… you speak many languages?",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359854",
      "answerText": "Can"
    }
  },
  "688552": {
    "questionText": "Smoking is very unhealthy. You … stop it!",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359860",
      "answerText": "must"
    }
  },
  "688553": {
    "questionText": "He … speak Arabic fluently when he was a child and they lived in Morocco.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359868",
      "answerText": "could"
    }
  },
  "688554": {
    "questionText": "… I ask a question? Yes, of course.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359869",
      "answerText": "may"
    }
  },
  "688555": {
    "questionText": "...at school yesterday.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359875",
      "answerText": "Were you"
    }
  },
  "688556": {
    "questionText": "Is your family large? ...",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359879",
      "answerText": "Yes, it is"
    }
  },
  "688557": {
    "questionText": "What ...he want?",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359884",
      "answerText": "does"
    }
  },
  "688558": {
    "questionText": "... do you have dinner?",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359890",
      "answerText": "What time"
    }
  },
  "688559": {
    "questionText": "He ... to go home.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359896",
      "answerText": "didn’t want"
    }
  },
  "688560": {
    "questionText": "Where ... to school?",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359899",
      "answerText": "did you go"
    }
  },
  "688561": {
    "questionText": "The boy ... cake when his mother came into the room.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359906",
      "answerText": "was eating"
    }
  },
  "688562": {
    "questionText": "She ... with her friends on Facebook every day.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359910",
      "answerText": "communicates"
    }
  },
  "688563": {
    "questionText": "I ... to Peru on holiday next month.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359914",
      "answerText": "am flying"
    }
  },
  "688564": {
    "questionText": "Oh! It .... I’ll take an umbrella with me.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359922",
      "answerText": "’s raining"
    }
  },
  "688565": {
    "questionText": "Do you have any plans for tonight? Yes, we ... to the cinema.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359927",
      "answerText": "are going"
    }
  },
  "688566": {
    "questionText": "This restaurant is ... the one over there.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359931",
      "answerText": "more traditional than"
    }
  },
  "688567": {
    "questionText": "My coffee was ... yours. I almost burned by mouth.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359934",
      "answerText": "hotter than"
    }
  },
  "688568": {
    "questionText": "The ... coffee in the world comes from Indonesia.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359942",
      "answerText": "most expensive"
    }
  },
  "688569": {
    "questionText": "I ... sushi.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359947",
      "answerText": "have never eaten"
    }
  },
  "688570": {
    "questionText": "She has ... finished this week’s report.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359950",
      "answerText": "already"
    }
  },
  "688571": {
    "questionText": "In the future there ... cures to the world’s worst diseases.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359954",
      "answerText": "might be"
    }
  },
  "688572": {
    "questionText": "I’ve received 33 emails ... .",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359962",
      "answerText": "this week"
    }
  },
  "688573": {
    "questionText": "...'s your name? Thomas.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359966",
      "answerText": "What"
    }
  },
  "688574": {
    "questionText": "This is Lucy and her brother, Dan. ... my friends.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359972",
      "answerText": "They're"
    }
  },
  "688575": {
    "questionText": "Oh, ... are my keys!",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359975",
      "answerText": "These"
    }
  },
  "688576": {
    "questionText": "What is ...?",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359981",
      "answerText": "Mary's job"
    }
  },
  "688577": {
    "questionText": "... are the keys? On the table.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359986",
      "answerText": "Where"
    }
  },
  "688578": {
    "questionText": "She ... a dog.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359992",
      "answerText": "doesn't have"
    }
  },
  "688579": {
    "questionText": "... at school last week?",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3359996",
      "answerText": "Were you"
    }
  },
  "688580": {
    "questionText": "He ... tennis with me yesterday.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3360002",
      "answerText": "didn't play"
    }
  },
  "688581": {
    "questionText": "Gina is married to John. He's her ... .",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3360005",
      "answerText": "husband"
    }
  },
  "688582": {
    "questionText": "We usually ... the shopping in a supermarket.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3360010",
      "answerText": "do"
    }
  },
  "688583": {
    "questionText": "I love this watch! It's ... .",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3360016",
      "answerText": "beautiful"
    }
  },
  "688584": {
    "questionText": "He doesn't have a car so he often uses public ... .",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3360020",
      "answerText": "transport"
    }
  },
  "688585": {
    "questionText": "He … at work now.",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3360025",
      "answerText": "isn’t"
    }
  },
  "688586": {
    "questionText": "… she play any musical instrument?",
    "categoryId": "10968",
    "answer": {
      "answerId": "3360029",
      "answerText": "Does"
    }
  }
}